{
    "subject": "Anna_Lee",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Robert_Nathan",
    "human_readable": "Anna Lee is married to Robert Nathan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9489895105361938,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Anna Lee and Robert Nathan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962973356246948,
            "question": "Who is Anna Lee married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8260743021965027,
            "question": "To whom is Anna Lee wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8140764832496643,
            "question": "Is Robert Nathan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731108069419861,
            "question": "Are Anna Lee and Robert Nathan partners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7650896310806274,
            "question": "Who is Anna Lee's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7051209211349487,
            "question": "Does Robert Nathan have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972792744636536,
            "question": "Who are Anna Lee and Robert Nathan related to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5279852747917175,
            "question": "What is the name of Robert Nathan's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274684429168701,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Robert Nathan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anna Lee is married to Robert Nathan.",
            "html": "yago_29602_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Robert Nathan's wife?",
            "html": "yago_29602_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Anna Lee and Robert Nathan related to each other?",
            "html": "yago_29602_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Robert Nathan have a spouse?",
            "html": "yago_29602_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29602_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Anna Lee was married to writer Robert Nathan, with the marriage occurring on 5 April 1970 and lasting until his death in 1985. This information supports the triple stating that Anna Lee is married to Robert Nathan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}